ekmpowershop1.com 2015-03-21

# Ekm Systems Privacy Policy

At Ekm Systems Ltd we are committed to protecting and respecting the privacy or all our customers and visitors.

The information collected from customers when signing up is used for billing and administration purposes only and will be kept confidential. Contact information collected will be contact details and payment information (credit or debit card).

When visitors use the website, information such as the ISP's domain, the time accessed and the pages visited will be stored by us. This is to analyse the web traffic and improve content of the site.

This site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as text you type in this website. This site does not use ClickTale to collect any personally identifiable information entered in this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information see [Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service](http://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx). We are using the information collected by ClickTale service to improve our website, make it more user-friendly and monitor that it is performing correctly. You can choose to disable the Service at <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>.

Any personal information contained within customer's websites and online shops is their own responsibility. We have taken security measures to ensure that our customers are protected against loss, alteration or misuse.

Customers are responsible for ensuring that only authorised personnel access their accounts. If for any reason you are concerned about this, please contact us on [abuse@ekmpowershop.com](mailto:abuse@ekmpowershop.com). Should you have any queries relating to our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [sales@ekmpowershop.com](mailto:sales@ekmpowershop.com).

## Cookies set by ekmPowershop.com

When browsing the internet and using online services, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your web enabled device, this includes small files known as cookies. They cannot be used to identify you personally.

Cookies are used to improve services for you, for example:

  * Enabling a site to recognise your web enabled device so you don't have to repeat information already given
  * Recognising that you may already have username and password so you don't need to enter this every time your requested
  * Measuring how many people are using the site, so usability can be improved

You can read more about these small files yourself, via the following link [Internet browser cookies - what they are and how to manage them](http://www.direct.gov.uk/en/SiteInformation/Cookies/DG_WP201851?CID=Central&PLA=url_mon&CRE=managing_cookies).

ekmPowershop.com uses cookies in several places we've listed each of them below with more details about why we use them and how long they will last.

Name | Purpose | Content | Expires  
---|---|---|---  
whoson | Live Chat System | Unique ID  | 2020  
ekmPowershop_cookie | Ascertains your country to deliver correct currency | Your country and currency | On Exit  
ASP Session ID | Tracks your visit to our website | Unique ID | On Exit  
  
## Logging in to the ekmPowershop system

After viewing our website and logging into our ekmPowershop.com system, you will receive more cookies to allow for a more bespoke user experience, these cookies are listed below. 

Name | Purpose | Content | Expires  
---|---|---|---  
ekmpowershop | Authentication Cookie | TestCookies=ACTIVE&RS=FALSE&  
logged_in=USERNAME&ServerID=***  | 72hrs - (3 days)  
demoshop_accessed | Stores a reference to the specific demoshop the visitor was using. | username=demoshop2 | On Exit  
ekmPowershop_website | Logs your username | username=***&accessed=YES | 144hrs - (6 days)  
ekm_USERNAME | Testing to see if Cookies are Enabled | CookieTest=ENABLED&uid=*** | N/A  
ekmPowershop_Trans_Cookie | Stores whether jQuery menu transition effects are enabled. | 

    TransitionOff=False

| N/A  
  
## Your shop visitors Cookies

If you have an online shop with us, your shop itself will deliver cookies to your visitors browser, these are listed below. 

Name | Purpose | Content | Expires  
---|---|---|---  
ekm_USERNAME | Temporary cookie generated to test if cookies are enabled on the visitors browser. | TestCookies=ACTIVE&RS=FALSE&  
logged_in=USERNAME&ServerID=***  | 72 hrs (3 days)  
ekm_pp_USERNAME | Stores a unique reference to visitors cart contents. Stores authentication details for customer logged in section. | Unique ID | On Exit  
ekm_tmp_ORDERNUMBER | Stores a reference to the visitors order number after an order has been generated. | Unique ID | On Exit  
  
## Third Party Cookies

We use a number of third party suppliers who may also set cookies on their websites. ekmPowershop.com doesn't control the usage of these cookies. You should check the third party websites for more information about these.

Third Party | Name | Purpose | Info  
---|---|---|---  
Google | _utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to create reports and to help us improve the overall website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. | [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/policies/privacy/)  
Facebook | cc_social | Facebook tracking code | On Exit  
Vimeo | aka_debug | Remembers vimeo settings | On Exit
